

#### FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2703 Loraine St. Lynchburg, VA 24504

🛮 (434) 406-0334 | 🗷 brooklyn\_welsh@outlook.com | 🎁 brooklynwelsh.com | 🖸 BrooklynWelsh | 🛅 brooklyn-welsh

# Summary\_

Current Full Stack Developer at CACI International Inc.. 2.5 years experience specializing both backend and frontend web development. Experience with serveral languages and frameworks, including JavaScript/TypeScript, React, Python, and more. Loves to learn new, cutting edge web technologies and frameworks.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

### **CACI International Inc.**

Rome, NY (Remote)

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Feb. 2021 - Present

- Secured extended contracts and funding for CACI by leading a team of 3 interns on a scheduling and event visualization app for a DoD customer.
- Provided code reviews and feedback to interns in an Agile environment to ensure code quality and meet customer requirements
- Created a new contract opportunity for CACI by pioneering a proof of concept app which integrated a NodeJS app with a Cyber Operations program developed by another company. Communicated with their dev team and CACI managers to stay informed on architecture, request or clarify app capabilities, and submit bug reports.
- Developed an app in an Agile/Scrum environment, which integrated with a suite of apps written in Java, Python, and JavaScript. Utilizes SQL stored procedures, functions, triggers, etc. to ensure efficient and strict adherence to the data model required.
- Improved code maintainability by implementing unit and integration tests on an existing project using Mocha and Sinon. Wrote Selenium tests to ensure functionality of the frontend.
- Supported an R&D contract by creating a suite of Python scripts which reads in a remote SQL schema, generates randomized queries categorized by runtime complexity, and runs them against the database while gathering performance data.
- Implemented Gitlab CI/CD changes to run installation, testing, linting, and documentation generation steps in parallel, cutting pipeline run time and resource usage by 50%.

University of Lynchburg

Lynchburg, VA

LINUX/UNIX INTERNSHIP

2019 - 2020

- Ensured department Linux machines were up to date with latest security updates.
- Maintained department website, including backups, migrations, security, and all site updates.
- Wrote scripts in both Bash and Perl which were executed for every new user created on the machine as part of user account management.
- Worked as a team with one other intern to carry out any administration tasks set out by the professor each week and maintained documentation of steps needed to reproduce.

# **Education**

## University of Lynchburg

Lynchburg, VA

Aug. 2013 - Nov. 2020

• B.S. in Computer Science

# **Projects**

### **Image to ASCII Converter**

WRITTEN WITH REACT, NEXTJS, TYPESCRIPT AND TAILWINDCSS

- User can scale images for more or less resolution, and control font size.
- Offloads image processing to a Web Worker to keep UI responsive.
- Image controls (resolution, scaling) are connected to ASCII conversion script using react state/props.
- Completely responsive on all screen sizes.
- Hosted with Github Pages at brooklynwelsh.github.io/img-to-ascii/

### **Personal Website**

BROOKLYNWELSH.COM

- Static website generated with NextJS and TailwindCSS, hosted with Github Pages.
- Resume markup filled using JSON file, plan on integrating with a headless CMS.